[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "If I was Justin Bieber, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "Put the seatbelt on, buddy, because it's going to be a bumpy ride.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "You've admitted to one dose of Botox?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Oh, yes, I tried it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Do they really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "It's so cool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "It must still give you even you guys a buzz, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "It's an ego builder, let me tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "If you're ever feeling bad about yourself, you just drive past the Flamingo and it's like the biggest billboard in the city.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Did you ever imagine in the '70s when you started that show, did you ever imagine that here you'd be 40 years later doing this in Vegas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "No, I mean, you know, you think about a career.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vegas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "And it's nice to be out there with somebody who they can tell if something's not working and they're there to cover each other or whatever it is, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "It just happened the other night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "You can completely trust each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Whoever else you work with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marie"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What's the thing that takes you to that level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I don't know if I speak on behalf of Marie, but when we put this show together, you could throw as much money as you want at a show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 132, "question": "What are you laughing at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "We did --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "We did QVC the other day, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Don't go into that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["QVC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Learning from old school.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 157, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "But who would you like to --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Who of all the greats that played in Vegas mould you most like to have seen in a theater like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "RBS", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "We did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "You saw them all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "We worked with them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Did you perform with Sasha and Sinatra?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sasha", "Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "And Sammy Davis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sammy Davis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Dean Martin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Elvis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Elvis in Vegas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Lucille Ball.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vegas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "So being a proper star, really, from what you're saying is, look out to an audience and making them feel as important as they're making you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Do you remember what Groucho Marx did to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho Marx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho Marx"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Groucho Marx?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Groucho Marx.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho Marx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Serious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "He was on the \"Donny and Marie Show\" and -- yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "What was John Wayne like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "John Wayne was a very stoic man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "He talked like this really, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "He was John Wayne.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Why does the maiden who keeps a crackling fire on such a frosty day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Sir, you cannot imagine how glad I am to see you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "That's the most exciting thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Well, because you got married to a guy you married before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Tell me how did -- how did this happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "You got married how long ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "It's been 29 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What was -- what was wrong then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "You know, Piers, I think too young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "You remarried, but he never did, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "No, he never remarried, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Oh, yes, I'd been divorced almost, what, six years now or something like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "WDT", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "So you were a single woman, and he was a single guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Did your son know that you were dating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "How long did you keep it from him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "When we told him we were getting married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "And your son is, what, nearly 30 now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", ",", "RB", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "He's 28.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "What was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I thought it was fantastic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "I mean, for any brother, when you see a sister have her heartbroken as you said you did the first time when the marriage fell apart, doesn't part of you feel that protective thing, I hope this doesn't happen again with this guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP$", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Let's go one step further, it's always been uncomfortable between -- at least for me, between us, that I have a very successful marriage for 33 years and she didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Was there a moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "You know, the only thing I can say is when it's right, it's really right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Do you think that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I just think I'm a hard habit to break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "When you saw yourself -- and what did you think, Donny, when you saw her in that dress again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "It was beautiful.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Did you get it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What do you want to talk to me about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, actually a sort of serious thing, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Shall I leave?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "No, I want you to stay.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Did you choose that day deliberately or was it just a freak coincidence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "No, I chose it deliberately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Yes, completely, I get that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Would she have been happy, your mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Oh, that would have been something my mother -- yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "And put Michael's picture.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "What's the reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "You never get over that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "It's just the worst parental nightmare, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Well, you know, God says you go through the sorrow to know the joys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "You felt his presence on your wedding day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Flamingo"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Donny, what was it like for to you see your sister go through such a crushing tragedy and be working with her at the same time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "You can only imagine what we went through here at the Flamingo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Is it a way of getting back into your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I think you've got to be careful about that, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Did you draw a great comfort from the audience reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "You know, everybody will have their reasons for doing things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "When you say Donny was your rock, in what way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Well, you know, he could tell I was hurting.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "When we come back, I want to talk to you about the door marked fame that you two were shoved through when you were very young?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I remember when you asked me this question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Piers", "Piers"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Would still want to go through that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Oh, Piers, Piers, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Osmond"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Oh, the Osmonds, the other ones?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Every girl I got my eye on, age -- I don't know -- nine or 10, didn't want to know because she had Donny bloody Osmond on her wall.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osmonds"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Do you remember when the balconies collapsed from the weight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "If I could take you back to the door marked fame and give you the option not to go through that, to lead a completely normal, anonymous life, without everything that fame brings, would you take that option?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "If I could have it the way I have it at this very moment, I would walk through that door.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "What he's going to go through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "He's going through so much heartache.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Do you still hate \"Puppy Love\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "No, I love -- I was just about to say, I've gone through many, many doors where I have actually made full circle and I've embraced \"Puppy Love\" to where I absolutely enjoy singing that song.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "There be have moments in your career when \"Puppy Love\" has been this massive millstone around your neck, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Yes, it was a millstone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Is it inevitable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "He's got it now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "If I was Justin Bieber, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "Put the seat belt on, buddy, because it's going to be a bumpy ride.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "What finally brought you back to recording?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "Well, I had to wait until she stopped playing with dolls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "Was it fun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "Well, you know -- I don't know fun is the right word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Is it hard or easy to be with your own brother when you're making a record?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "Oh, you know, I think initially --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny", "Marie"]}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Are you pleasantly surprised?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Yes, I have to say I'm pleasantly surprised because, because Donny and Marie is a big target.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "Why do you say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "I'm serious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "Why would you care what the rock audience think of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "To be honest with you, I don't care anymore, because I am who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 827, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "It's what you look like is unique to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 847, "question": "Every day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 848, "answer": "Not every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "I have never -- well, accidentally a couple times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 856, "question": "Never taken drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 857, "answer": "Never had a desire to take drugs, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "You are Mr. Squeaky clean, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Well, you know what, if that's what it takes to live a good life, yeah, call me squeaky clean.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 866, "question": "-- sexuality, all that kind of stuff in their lyrics and so on, do you feel offended?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 867, "answer": "First of all, let me just make the statement, I think Lady Gaga is brilliant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 878, "question": "It's like who wants that kind of face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 879, "answer": "Marie, talk me through this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 892, "question": "Why don't we pretend you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 893, "answer": "I like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 896, "question": "But what else do you do to keep in this kind of shape?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 897, "answer": "Well, I mean, I lost 50 pounds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "Do you exercise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 904, "question": "How long are you going to be performing here, for starters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 905, "answer": "Until the end of this year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "Is there anywhere you'd rather be performing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "There's all kinds of opportunities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 917, "question": "When you finish up here, the shows -- because you're playing tonight -- what do you go out on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 918, "answer": "We just changed the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "qSentId": 926, "question": "But the ones that we can't take out of the show is like -- what do we end the show with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 927, "answer": "May tomorrow be a perfect day", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 940, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 941, "answer": "Well, sing me the song.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 959, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 960, "answer": "Wait.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 971, "question": "Is this the new side of you that we're learning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 972, "answer": "It's just a tender side I hide so cleverly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]